[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
Gandang Gabi,
Kapamilya   and   Kapuso!
- Gandang Gabi, Vice!
Yes! It's already late
and you're still so loud!
- People are already asleep!
- [CHEERING, APPLAUSE CONTINUES]
It's already past 10PM
and you're all still up!
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
Didn't I tell you
to go to bed early...
...to prepare for
the upcoming week?!
It's already Monday tomorrow!
Why are you staying up late?!
I'm telling you, you'll all
be like zombies tomorrow.
But I can't blame you.
I know you can't sleep
and let the week end
without witnessing my beauty.
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
Yeah!
It's the kind of beauty you'll
want to see to end the weekend.
Amen?
- Amen!
You all had a busy week
and you'll end it
just like that?
You have to end with a bang!
[CHEERING]
Yes! Definitely!
And since you are all here,
we cannot be incomplete.
So, let me call in
my Geng Gang!
- Yes!
- Let's go!
- Whoo!
- [VICE] Come here! Come here!
Verna...
Tetay, and of course...
Vince Maristela is finally here!
Yes!
Wow! So this is how
it feels like to be on  GGV!
You just found out now because
you missed our pilot episode!
- You weren't there for Alden.
- [CHUCKLES SHYLY]
Oh, let it slide. He was sick!
But now, he's fine!
He's finally here with us!
[AUDIENCE, HOSTS CHEERING]
Yeah, we need some
eye candy here.
Who'd want to watch a show
with hosts that look
like horses and dogs, right?
- Yeah, Tetay.
- Dogs, horses, and monkeys.
- [LAUGHTER]
- We're all animals.
At least someone here
is pleasant to look at.
- Viewers won't get sick of us.
- Yes.
He's a looker, right?
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- Yes!
- Look at that!
You're going to melt him
with your stares.
He's been staring at me since
we were in the dressing room.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
He was staring to make sure
he knew who to sue
if he lost something.
So he can describe
what the thief looks like.
Why don't you greet
our  Kapamilya  and  Kapuso?
Gandang Kapamilya--
Oh, I got it wrong.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Maybe this'll be
his last day on here.
But it was just his first day!
[LAUGHS]
It'll be his last day.
Gandang Gabi,
Kapamilya  and  Kapuso!
- [CHEERING]
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
How was your week?
- How was your week?
- Oh! That's good!
- You all okay?
- Yes!
- You survived?
Very good.
It's a privilege to be able
to survive every week.
- True.
- How was your week, guys?
Verna, how was your week?
I've had a fun week, Meme.
We celebrated
my son's birthday.
We went out.
Look at that. She got pregnant.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
And the man didn't even know.
- Yeah!
- She got pregnant.
Just with saliva. That's it.
Then her belly grew.
It was your son's birthday.
You celebrated what?
- Hhis second birthday.
- He knows you're his mother?
Mm-hmm.
Do you think
it was a happy birthday?
It was a happy birthday.
What are you saying?
You're a godmother.
Oh, gosh! I forgot
I'm his godmother!
[TETAY] Yeah, we both are.
What did you do
for his birthday party?
We went out.
Just a family outing.
We went to the Manila Zoo.
- Ah, really? How was it?
- In all fairness,
the entrance was free.
Why do you have a free
entrance privilege there?
I don't know either.
Maybe they were like,
"Feel at home!"
[LAUGHTER]
The entrance was free
but we couldn't find the exit.
- Why?
- I don't know.
They didn't let us go home.
We spent the night there.
[LAUGHTER]
Vince, how was your week?
It's pretty solid.
I'm blessed work-wise.
And the highlight of
my weekend last week
was my friend
who asked me
if I'm down to go on a date.
Blind date?
Your friend asked you to go
on a blind date with them?
No, no. They're hooking me up
with another person.
- Ah.
- Introduced you to someone.
Oh, so you went on a blind date?
You went home
without even seeing each other.
No, no.
- It was you, wasn't it?
- [LAUGHTER]
That's why we covered his eyes.
You went on a blind date.
- No, no. I didn't.
- You didn't say yes?
It's hasn't been set.
But I'm still hesitating
whether to go or not.
Why? What are the things
you're considering?
Why do you have hesitations?
For one, I'm still a virgin.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- [TETAY] It's just a date!
- I'm joking!
You're not going
to do the deed right away!
I'm just joking!
Women aren't easy.
Come on. I'm just joking.
What...
Did you do the deed
right on the first date?
No! I'm not easy, Meme.
I waited three days.
Not right on the first date.
[LAUGHTER]
So you didn't have
any idea at all
or was it a fake blind date?
Or you really don't know who.
No idea at all.
But I guess
I'm having doubts
because I'm not sure if
I'm ready for commitment.
- Ah...
- Because when you start dating,
you have to be ready.
- So...
- But it's just casual dating.
But I read somewhere that...
nowadays,
men aren't looking for dates
or aren't
pursuing relationships.
Men nowadays don't date
or enter relationships.
It's not an issue of attraction.
But...
- They want to...
- There are...
There are a lot of
horror stories
about relationships.
Failed relationships.
Toxic relationships.
Things like that.
So men are fine without them.
They're not eager
to get into relationships.
[VINCE] I agree. We prefer
things to happen naturally.
[VICE] Yes.
They just want to have fun.
With or without a relationship.
They don't want to
force anything.
- [TETAY] Okay.
- Aren't you in a relationship?
- Yeah.
- But you're not a straight man.
We're referring to straight men.
But when my partner
was courting me,
I also asked myself,
"Am I ready for this?"
- Because...
- Ah.
- I said--
- But isn't that forbidden?
Isn't it illegal in Saudi Arabia
for men to be courted?
[IN DEEP VOICE] Wow!
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Because I'm a camel?
[LAUGHING]
- But that's very interesting.
- Mm-hmm.
How was your week?
Oh, it was splendid.
Like, it was perfect.
- The usual stuff.
- [VICE] Splendid, really?
Okay, I'll just use Splenda.
[LAUGHS]
- But it was great.
- [VICE] The sweetener?
Isn't that
an artificial sweetener?
Yes!
I spent time with the kids.
I also got to work on
other projects.
We went to my OB-GYN.
I got a checkup.
- OB-GYN?
- Yes.
Yes, my doctor
circumcised me instead.
"This is what you really need!"
"This will get you
to shut up!"
Wow, going to an OB-GYN
is a fantasy for some gay men.
Then my doctor said,
"He's lost it!"
But the doctor still took you in
- to collect the fee.
- Yes.
But what about you?
How was your week?
Well, I had a very loaded week.
- Whoa!
- Wow!
We accomplished a lot.
- That's right!
- Yes!
It's like I had 36 hours a day.
- Yes.
- Like I'm only 26 years old.
I'm very happy I achieved a lot.
I just started filming
a new movie.
- Yes.
- We just started shooting.
Ooh! It's almost MMFF!
We're looking forward
to your movie!
You better be!
If you don't watch it,
I'll make sure you regret it.
Please catch the
Metro Manila Film Festival
on December 25!
It has become our tradition.
And this time, I will be
with Vic "Bossing" Sotto!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
[TETAY] How incredible.
Your schedule is packed with
work, taping,
and everything else
You even have   It's Showtime.
You're so busy.
But how do you maintain
your beauty?
Some people find that
impossible to do.
You make it look effortless!
Do you always feel that way?
Do you feel beautiful every day?
Hmm. I don't know.
Like...
I feel sorry for other people
who need to do so much.
[TETAY] Oh, there she goes!
- [CHUCKLES]
- But I think...
It's the genes and the jeans.
- [LAUGHTER]
- So I'm in denim today.
But seriously,
when you're inspired,
when you love
what you're doing,
when you're excited about
everything you're going to do,
what you do
doesn't feel like work.
It feels like I'm trying
something new every time.
- So it's exciting.
- [TETAY] And you're having fun.
I get to work with a lot
of new people in this film,
which makes me very happy.
Wait, where's my phone?
Oh...
Mister Mel, you still
don't know our SOP?
You know I need my phone.
While I was hosting,
I was wondering where it was.
- I just had it.
- Here it is.
We've been through this before.
If you're short on cash,
let us know.
You don't have to
resort to stealing.
- [TETAY] Have some empathy.
- Come on, Mister Mel.
[TETAY] He's got bills to pay.
- I know.
- [VERNA] Life is hard.
You know, when he was
working on  It's Showtime,
a lot of folks lost their phone,
but they didn't report it.
- [TETAY] Mister Mel!
- [DRAMATIC STING]
- [VERNA] Oh my goodness.
- We just ignored it.
Whoa! Oh my...
I forgot I put my phone
in my back pocket.
It feels nice when someone calls
while it's on vibrate mode.
- Don't pick up yet!
- Oh!
- Let it ring.
- Someone's calling...
- but I don't want to pick up!
- [VERNA LAUGHS]
Because-- It's really vibrating!
Do you hear it?
[TETAY]
I think I heard you fart.
- [PHONE BUZZING]
- It's vibrating.
Wait.
- [VERNA] It was ringing.
- [TETAY] During work hours?
See?
It's a very important message.
[VERNA] What did they say?
"Missed FaceTime audio call."
Oh, they're calling again.
- Unlock it first.
- Swipe up.
- What do you mean?
- Oh my.
Wait a minute!
Is that really your phone?
This is embarrassing.
This is my phone!
The wallpaper is
a picture of Ion and me.
It's an unregistered number.
Oh, it's Mac! It's Macmac.
Hello?!
[JM]  H-Hello, Vice?
J--
- J--
- [GUSHING, SQUEALING]
Sorry, I'm at a beer house
right now.
It's so loud in here.
[LOUD CHEERS]
Why did you call?
I'm filming.
[JM]   It sure is loud out ther.
I just want to ask...
have you seen Fyang?
[AUDIENCE GUSHING]
You aren't with her?
No.
She said we'd meet there.
- Why--
- Is she with you?
The last time I saw her
was during filming yesterday.
Don't... Don't you know
where he is?
No, she's not picking up.
I'm getting annoyed.
I'm taping GGV.
Where are you?
Yeah. On my way...
I'm on my way to ABS-CBN.
I'll drop by.
Just come over here. Come here,
we'll talk about it here.
I can't understand you,
it's too noisy!
Come here if you're nearby
anyway. Bye-bye.
Yes, Vice. Thank you. Thank you.
- Okay, bye.
- [SQUEALS] Oh my god!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- Oh my god.
This is mine!
Look at the wallpaper.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Can I see? Wow!
- Wow! Inspired!
- You haven't experienced it.
I have.
Your wallpaper had different
breeds of dogs.
- [DOORBELL DINGS]
- He's here!
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
It's so noisy inside this house.
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- [DOORBELL CHIMES]
- [TETAY SCREAMS]
- JM!
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
What?
Why are you all alone?
Hi!
- Here's your Auntie Tetay.
- Come say hi.
- Auntie Tetay.
- Here's Vince.
Oh, that's your old nanny.
She just got back
from Abu Dhabi.
The noise is driving me crazy!
I've been annoyed, Vice.
Where have you been?
I've been looking for Fyang.
What was your agreement?
Nothing, we...
We supposedly have a date.
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- Whoo!
Where were you supposed to meet?
Here, she said, at ABS-CBN.
- You don't know where she went?
- No.
She hasn't been replying or
answering my calls for a while.
Oh my god!
Here comes the question
on everyone's mind.
Where's Fyang?!
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Fyang!
- Where are you, Fyang?!
- [VINCE]Fyang!
- Where's Fyang?!?
- Fyang!
- Where? Where can we find her?
- Bring Fyang out!
- [VERNA] Where is Fyang?!
- Where are you?
Look over there.
Go ahead and check.
- Where's Fyang?!
- Fyang! Fyang!
- That's not Fyang.
- No, no. Wrong person.
- Where is she?
- Fyang!
- She's not there.
- Let's look for her!
- Where's Fyang?
- Come with me!
[CHUCKLES] Why?
Did you laugh at Fyang?
- Where is she?
- [VICE GANDA] Help us out.
Let's look for Fyang!
- Where's Fyang?
- Hey, Fyang!
- Fyang!
- Fyang! Where are you, Fyang?
- Where's Fyang?
- Fyang, come out now!
- Fyang!
Hey, Fyang!
Where are you? Come out!
Fyang!
Fyang, where are you, Fyang?
- Fyang, come out already!
- Fyang!
JM, what did she say?
Where did she say she was going?
I really don't know.
She didn't mention it.
I've been annoyed all this time,
I can't find her anywhere.
Fyang!
Maybe she's
by the water dispenser.
Where is Fyang?!
- Bring Fyang out!
- Where?
- You too. Where's Fyang?
- Did you see her?
Bring her out!
Bring Fyang out!
Is this Fyang?
- It's Fyang!
- [TETAY LAUGHING]
Where's Fyang?
- You're playing around again...
- That's not her!
- Not her!
- Carlito!
Going to ABS-CBN just to play
around and act all extra?
Your zipper's open!
Your zipper's open.
[LAUGHTER]
- Fyang!
- Where's Fyang?
- JM, where is Fyang?
I really can't find her.
Where on earth is she?
- I can't--
- [SHRIEKS] Fyang!
[PEOPLE SQUEALING]
- JM has been looking for you.
- I'm charging my phone.
Quiet for a moment!
Why are you here?
I'm charging, my battery died.
- He couldn't call you!
- I couldn't call you.
I've been so annoyed.
How could you call me
when my phone was dead?
Couldn't you at least
charge it before leaving?
- It was dead!
- We have a date, right?
Stop being dramatic,
my phone was dead!
Oh my god!
- In this part of ABS-CBN...
- Oh, what now?
- And later, it'll be my fault.
- There's a love team...
- Since when is it my fault?
- ...having a misunderstanding.
- I was charging it.
- Where could this conflict
be heading?
Will this lead to a real fight
and the eventual breakup
of their love team?
We'll find out all of that
when the best Sunday night
habit returns, this is...
[ALL]  Gandang Gabi Vice!
They're still fighting.
My phone was dead!
Why does it sound
like it's my fault?
When did this become my fault?
Why is it always men's fault?
- When did it become my fault?
- It's always me.
You're so dramatic.
Oh my God.
Okay, let's go.
- [CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
- [THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Joining us tonight
in spreading good vibes
is one of the most
trending  Kapamilya love teams!
Gandang Gabi,
JM Ibarra and Fyang Smith!
Yes! Hello!
Gandang Gabi,
Kapamilya  and  Kapuso!
- [VICE] Yes!
- [CHEERING CONTINUES]
At last, I finally get to
interview JM and Fyang!
We've made a million attempts,
- but none pushed through.
- Actually, you're right.
- They're that busy! [CHUCKLES]
- [FYANG LAUGHS]
But now, it's finally happening.
- You look so fresh!
- Thank you, Meme!
As if I didn't just come
from a, you know... Right?
- From a hectic schedule?
- Yeah.
Can you do that again?
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Did I slay? [CHUCKLES]
This kid really exudes aura,
while he's super nonchalant.
See what he did?
He just moved to the side.
[AUDIENCE CHUCKLING]
He's always like that!
Show us--
Flex a little!
- Let's do that.
- Flex a little.
Let's flex those looks.
Let's do a, um...
- ...face card check!
- Okay!
Very Gen Z.
Let's do a face card check.
Let's start with Fyang.
Face card check, go!
- [DOWNBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[VICE] That's the face
everyone's talking about.
Every move she makes
and every time
she opens her mouth,
she gets the whole town talking!
That's the face card
of a trending celebrity
of the nation.
Yes!
JM, your turn.
- Let's see how he'll flex.
- How do I do it?
You can do it!
Stop pretending you can't!
- [VICE LAUGHS]
- You can do it.
You're a guy.
You guys do it differently.
- Okay, turn around first.
- I thought I had to copy her.
[FYANG, AUDIENCE LAUGH]
C-Copy her?!
You're gonna do this and that?
Don't ruin the fantasy
of your fans!
Okay, turn around.
- Go for it.
- Face card check for...
JM Ibarra!
[UPBEAT, SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICE] Yes!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- His face card is giving...
...pure-blooded
Filipino Gen Z!
He's also giving ripped
but gentle!
Very heartthrob material!
Why are you getting shy now?!
- I saw that lip bite!
- [FYANG] Me, too!
- Do it again! Show us!
- Bite your lip again!
Give it your all!
Like... Mm!
Give it some oomph!
That's enough.
Just imagine there are men
hitting on Fyang--
[JM] Fine. I'll do it.
- [VICE] You have to--
- Shoot here!
[VICE] "Shoot"?!
Wait! What do you mean
by "shoot"?
- Focus on me.
- The camera?
When he said, "Shoot here,"
I got nervous!
[LAUGHTER]
Not now.
Okay! Director, focus on him!
One more time, JM Ibarra!
- [SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING
[TETAY] My gosh!
[VICE] That's the kind of
face card that people choose!
- He's really shy, huh?
- Yeah.
I did everything I could
to help him.
- Is that the best he's got?
- Yeah.
You need to have the confidence
of my Geng Gang.
Show us your face cards.
Turn around first.
- [VINCE] Verna, stand up!
- [VERNA] I'm up!
- [VICE] She's already standing!
- Oh! Sorry! Sorry!
Geez, Vince!
Just like a Labrador!
[LAUGHTER]
[VICE] Okay. Turn around,
then show us your face card.
Let's start with...
Vince Maristela's
face card check.
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- [VICE] Yes.
That's the face card of
a hot and fit Gen Z!
Yes!
That's the perfect face card!
Next up, Verna!
- [SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
Look at her face.
It'll make you wonder...
Face card or phase out?
More like phase out, huh?
She's obsolete.
Barely being used.
Yes! She's giving fierce!
Looks like she
just got vaccinated.
Here comes Tetay.
Face card check, Tetay.
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Face card check.
It's giving someone who
is about to receive mass cards.
[LAUGHTER]
That's so mean!
Well, she's giving fish cart.
When you go to the market,
you can drag her along.
Can you show us again, Tetay?
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VICE] Check out those lips!
It's obvious they've visited
a certain clinic many times.
Thank your sponsor!
See? Now, it's so
plump and pouty.
- You can see, it's--
- Thank you so much!
[VICE] Like it's injected with
oil from some ship!
[CHUCKLING]
- Thank you.
- [AUDIENCE]  Vice! Vice! Vice!
- [TETAY] What's that?
- You do it too, Meme!
[AUDIENCE, HOSTS CHANTING]
Vice Ganda! Vice Ganda!
[TETAY]
Okay! Game! Game! Game!
Here we go!
One, two, three!
- Face card reveal!
- [SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Damn!
[LOUD CHEER]
[TETAY] See?
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Beauty that never takes a break.
- That's quite a smile, huh?
- Yes.
- Look at that.
- Those sparkling teeth.
Look at that! [CHUCKLES]
How are you?
[MUFFLED] I'm okay.
How about you guys?
- [TETAY LAUGHS]
- Are you guys okay?
Playtime's over.
Let's sit down for now.
- Okay. How long ago was PBB?
- [LOUD THUD]
What's that? Did you break
something again, Tetay!
- No--
- [VINCE LAUGHS]
- Nothing!
- It broke!
We don't have a budget,
so stop breaking things!
- No, I'm a majorette.
- [VERNA] It broke!
Careful with those chairs there,
or they might break.
Okay. How long ago was  PBB?
How many years has it been?
- Maybe two or three?
- Two?
- Two or three, but...
- Ah, two years.
- Two years.
But your batch
was such a riot, right?
A lot of people didn't
expect it to get that popular.
Yes.
Were you happy
with your experience there?
Because I've talked
to some people
who had a lot of opportunities
after leaving,
but others were like...
stressed out, overwhelmed,
you know?
That's how living in the house
affected them.
How about you guys?
Personally, Meme,
I'm happy because
it's something
I can honestly say I'll only
experience once in my life.
What do you mean?
Because not everyone
gets the chance
to enter Big Brother's house.
- Yeah.
- I mean...
You're really rubbing it in
that I didn't make it
to the first-ever
celebrity edition.
I auditioned back then,
but I didn't get in.
- Really?
- Yes.
Which season?
The first-ever
celebrity edition,
the one Keanna Reeves won.
- Oh!
- I auditioned back then.
- Rejected.
- At least...
Out of all the people
who wanted to get in there,
you were one of the ones chosen.
- And you even won.
- I'm lucky.
- No regrets?
- None.
I mean...
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
- Be honest.
There are a few,
but I'm really happy.
I'm so happy because
they also opened
so many opportunities for me.
So I'm super happy and
grateful to  Big Brother.
What part do you regret?
I think maybe the part where
I talked about my family.
That's the part I regret.
I wish I hadn't opened up
about them.
- Why?
- Well, because now,
whenever I get bashed,
for example,
they also get attacked.
- So...
- They got dragged into it.
They get dragged into it because
I talked about them on   PBB.
That's really the only part
I regret. But...
As for my journey,
I'm super happy.
How about you?
Same. I'm happy that...
That's how it is, right?
You're happy with the
experience inside the house,
but I can't deny there were
also parts
that weren't great.
When we watch it,
it's exciting, right?
But when you're the ones inside,
is it exciting,
or is it more stressful?
Mm, 50-50.
It depends on
what happens, Meme.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
Because some people say
it's scripted.
But it really isn't scripted.
Whatever you actually do in...
It's edited,
but it's not scripted.
- Yes, it's super edited.
- Of course it is.
Wait, super edited?
That sounds like you're
trying to say something.
- She wants to say something.
- No, no.
Super edited?
- It is edited, yes.
- And Vince agreed.
- He said, "Yes."
- [LAUGHTER]
- Right?
- [VINCE GIGGLING]
"Yeah, super edited."
If it wasn't, you wouldn't
have been eliminated, right?
- Yeah, I believe that.
- [FYANG CHUCKLING]
That's one of my
personal gripes.
- He's getting sad again.
- It's one of your traumas.
That's my trauma.
Super edited.
At the end of the day, you
you guys really liked
each other, right?
Because there were
so many of you there.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Come on, should I answer it?
- You answer.
- Me?
Uh, inside the house,
we're really like best friends.
- Really?
- It's true!
- It's true, I promise!
- You didn't like him?
Okay, so you started as friends,
then you slowly
developed feelings?
- I mean...
- You started appreciating him,
then something romantic
started to bloom?
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- I mean...
Or did that happen
after you got out?
If I'm being honest...
wow, so dramatic? I mean...
He became my happy crush inside.
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- That's true, right?
- He knows that.
- You never told me that.
Whoa.
- You're only saying that now.
- No, you just think so!
And you didn't answer me
that way last time.
- GGV is getting special, huh?
- "Did you already like JM
from the start?"
Then you said, "No, I didn't.
I didn't like anyone
inside the house."
I mean, when it's a happy crush,
you're just amazed by
what kind of person someone is.
Because it was my first time
meeting someone like him.
Very manly.
Very old-school gentleman.
Why? Were all the people
you met before gay?
No! I mean...
The people I met before
were more like...
They wanted me
to boss them around.
- Ah...
- Like that.
Because it was really my
first time meeting a guy...
who had a mind of his own.
Because you have
a strong personality.
- Yes.
- Usually,
most of the guys you meet,
you eat them alive.
Yeah, Meme. Super!
You've eaten so many guys alive,
but you're still skinny, huh?
[LAUGHTER]
You stayed skinny.
Maybe the guys you ate
were all on a diet.
That's why you got
even skinnier.
- So, he's not submissive?
- No.
Oh, you fight back.
When she says she wants
things a certain way,
you do something different.
Yeah?
Especially when it's
for my own good.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
But you liked her
right away inside?
Actually, it seems like yes.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
I'm on your side.
I'm totally on your side.
[VICE CHUCKLING]
Really? She was the one
you liked right away inside?
Hey! You didn't answer me
that last time either.
Did you like her inside,
or did you only start liking her
after you got out? Be honest.
Liars get UTIs.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Honestly...
In terms of actually liking her,
- it was after we got out.
- You mean liking her like
you wanted to make
a move on her
- wanted to date her?
- Oh, that kind?
- Definitely after we got out.
- Ah, so not inside?
Who did you like inside?
Did you like someone else
in there?
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[FYANG] I'll tell them.
- Want me to?
- [VICE CHUCKLES]
Vince, I need your help.
[LAUGHTER]
If I were you,
I'd just follow her.
That way,
there won't be any fights.
- Exactly.
- Oh, that's how it is?
But this guy isn't even
submissive to girls.
- [VINCE] Oh, right.
- Yeah, yeah.
So why do you feel like
it wasn't you?
You think he liked
someone else inside?
- I don't really feel like...
- Oh my God!
JM, did Binsoy develop
feelings for you?
[LAUGHTER]
- Wasn't Binsoy in your batch?
- Yes, Meme.
No, I mean...
because at that time,
we were really just
best friends.
So, I wasn't expecting anything.
But who do you feel
he was into or liked inside?
I think no one.
Be honest.
If you ask me...
Wait, is it okay?
[VICE] Oh!
You're scared of JM.
I can feel it.
Because if it wasn't about him,
you don't care, you'll really
say whatever you want.
But when it's JM,
you actually consider things.
You hold yourself back
around him!
- No. Because...
- We're happy now, right?
We're happy.
So, going back to...
Wow, "we're happy now."
So, you actually have
a strong relationship...
[JM GIGGLES]
Are you guys dating now?
- [TETAY] Oh!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Uhm...
Am I really answering?
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- Do you want me to answer?
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
No, because when...
Those little acts you do,
like you're being all demure.
[CHUCKLES]
So sweet-smelling, so demure.
Are you guys a couple now?
Aren't you already a couple?
- It's been a while...
- Not yet.
- Die on it?
- Die on it.
We're not at that point yet...
- Not pee for three months?
- Not pee for three months.
I think that's already a UTI.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Not yet, Meme.
We're not rushing it.
Because...
If we're going to get there,
we want to enjoy
our journey first.
Together, of course.
Why won't you believe us?
Because that's not
what you told me last time.
[LAUGHTER]
How about you?
Don't you have anything to say?
You're sweating!
Are you okay?
[BOTH GIGGLE]
No, because you guys
have plans, right?
- Yes.
- So there's no need
- to rush everything.
- Mm-hmm.
There are still a lot of things
we need to prioritize.
Right.
You can say you're not dating,
but that doesn't mean...
You're already in love with her.
- All I know is, I like her.
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- She knows that.
- That was fast!
- [VICE] I'm so proud of you.
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
No. I've said it
so many times, right?
Oh!
Even if I'm not that vocal,
at least I said it.
What do you mean, bald?
- [JM LAUGHING]
- Fine, I'm quite bald.
[LAUGHTER]
Such a mouth on you!
"Not that vocal?"
Your hairline will rise, too,
when you're 50.
[CHUCKLING]
Okay, he's in love with you.
- I think...
- How about you?
- What do you mean, "I think"?
- I think...
I'll kick you...
You're getting on my nerves.
- [LAUGHTER]
- What?
Me? Yeah, of course.
- Because everything...
- Are you in love with him?
Yes. Of course I am.
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
It sounds like you're only
saying that now.
- No, I didn't!
- [LAUGHTER]
Because...
He has what I look for
in a guy.
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
What...
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
What do you look for in a guy?
- Uh...
- Didn't you mention that?
I asked you what you liked
about JM.
"He looks like he has a big..."
- Stop!
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
[VINCE LAUGHING]
Just kidding.
[CHUCKLING]
What is it...
Out of all the people
you've met,
what did you like most
about him, besides...
the fact that he has
a mind of his own...
Physically,
what did you see in him?
Physically, his teeth
are really nice.
And his nose
is really straight...
- His lips are really nice.
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- His lips.
- His lips are really nice.
- Have you kissed him already?
- Of course!
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- In Almost Us, right?
Just in that?
- Hey!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
He's the one spilling
the tea now, not you. Sorry.
- No. Wait.
- I made a mistake.
Because she told me,
"Meme, don't worry.
I'll be the one spilling the tea
because JM doesn't
really spill anything."
But then he started spilling
one line at a time.
He said, "Just in that?"
So it wasn't just there?
There was   Ghosting, too, righ?
I forgot about the Ghosting one.
[FYANG SIGHS]
When you guys kiss,
who's more nervous?
- The guy or the girl?
- What do you mean?
Of course,
when you guys kiss, right?
Isn't it nerve-racking?
Especially the first time?
For me, I was so scared
during my first kiss.
Because the last thing I ate
was dried fish,
so of course it was
embarrassing, right?
So, how does it feel?
Ah...
His lips are soft.
[VERNA SQUEALS]
Because, of course,
during our first kiss
in  Ghosting...
Why is the background music
like that?
It sounds like you're already
taking off each other's clothes.
We're just talking
about a kiss, right?
And this is from
the show, not real life.
- Yes.
- Sorry.
Our DJ is horny. Sorry.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
We're just talking about a kiss,
and you're already feeling
all sorts of things over there.
Come on!
Close your X-Tube.
[LAUGHTER]
I mean, because in  Ghosting,
it wasn't really a full-on kiss.
It wasn't really a full-on kiss?
So, what was it?
It was just a peck.
- With a hand?
- It's like here only.
- Oh.
[CHUCKLES]
- I hate you.
- Right?
So, when was
the actual full-on kiss?
In Almost Us.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
You, because
she described the kiss,
her experience, how about you?
- Me?
- How was it?
- I'm looking forward to...
- You're bouncing your leg.
- You want another one.
- That's right.
- One more!
- Can we do it now?
How does it work?
Does it happen slowly,
or is it just a quick one?
- [FYANG] It's slow.
- [JM] No, it's not.
- Reenact it.
- [VERNA] Sample!
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
What? A sample?
[LAUGHTER]
How? Do you slowly lean in,
or do you just go for it?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- She's killing it today!
- Meme!
- I think...
- You've changed.
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, Verna wants to do it
with Vince...
- Yeah, I think so!
- Sample!
I wonder what your lips
feel like, Verna?
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
Why? Haven't you kissed
your mom yet?
[LAUGHTER]
Kiss her and say,
"Happy Mother's Day."
In your opinion, Vince,
what does kissing Verna
feel like?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
It feels good on the cheek.
Why not on the lips?
- I'm good with the cheek.
- [LAUGHTER]
Pick one.
Let me see Tetay's lips
and Verna's as well.
Tetay's lips or Verna's lips?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, this is expensive.
It's brand-new.
- Tetay's.
- Mine are natural.
- Tetay's?
Okay, go.
You know, honestly, when...
- Tetay!
- I'm Tetay, idiot!
[LAUGHTER]
[TETAY] You bastard!
- [VINCE LAUGHING]
- You know...
I don't know if I should
be offended.
You know, actions speak
louder than words.
[CHUCKLES]
It's hilarious how you
turned his head around.
"I'm Tetay, idiot!"
You almost twisted
his head like that.
That's crazy.
Stop messing around.
They're going to kiss again.
- Come on!
- Yeah!
It's still early.
We're not giving it to you yet.
Yeah. Maybe in the last segment.
- In the last segment!
But I want to get
to know you guys.
What were you guys like
before you became actors?
Were you achievers in school?
Did you study hard?
What were you like?
- Did you graduate from college?
- I have one year left, Meme.
I stopped before I joined  PBB.
- But that wasn't the reason.
- What was your course?
- Air Transportation.
In the aviation field.
Ah, so you were going
to become a pilot?
- Hopefully.
- Were you smart in school?
Yeah, I'll say it myself. Yeah.
- Not really.
- Yeah?
I just like exploring
and trying different things.
Maybe Dora really is your name
on your birth certificate.
That's why you love exploring.
Why did you say
he's actually smart?
Because I just came
from their house in Mauban.
- Were his medals on display?
- Yeah, there were so many!
That's how it is
in the province, right?
I don't have those
in the province.
Your certificates
were even laminated.
There were so many, Meme.
Like...
One whole section was just
filled with his medals.
But your awards are real, right?
They weren't made in Recto?
- I had some of mine made.
- It's far from us.
Really?
But when you talk to
each other, you realize,
- "Oh, he really is smart."
- Yeah.
Especially when he
corrects me about things
that I thought were right
but were actually wrong.
- Really?
- Yes, he likes correcting me.
Were you a guidance counselor
before?
- [LAUGHTER]
- My dad was.
Were you smart
when you were in school?
- Just average.
- What do you mean by average?
I mean, I wasn't...
I feel like you were a slacker.
Just average, too.
CHUCKLES] How do you become
an average slacker?
You only did a number of
absences, is that it?
- Yes.
- Have you skipped school?
No, I've never
experienced that, Meme.
Do you hang out
with your friends a lot?
- No, not much.
- Do you have a fraternity?
No, we don't have that, Meme.
- Nothing?
- Yeah, nothing.
Because... uh--
How could I have cut class
back then, Meme?
You had to tap your ID,
then it would send
a notification
to your mom about...
- what time you left.
- Your school was so fancy!
- We don't have those!
- So fancy!
- It's true.
- What's your school?
Jose Rizal University.
- Is it really like that there?
- [FYANG] Yes!
What's that? An MRT?
It's true, Meme.
I'm not kidding.
- [VICE] That's so fancy.
- It's true.
Then your family gets notified
- [FYANG] Yes.
- if you went to school or not.
They get notified of what time
you went to school
- and what time you left.
- Your school is no fun.
- You can't skip school!
- [TETAY LAUGHS]
That's not fun.
During the second quarter,
I changed the number to my own.
- Ah, so...
- So I get notified.
- So you skipped school then?
- No.
Are you studious?
- Before.
- Do you go to the library?
- Yes.
- Do you recite a lot?
Recite? Yes!
What were you like
as a student?
What are you good at?
Um...
A lot.
- Wow!
I explored a lot.
I think I saw you host before.
- Hosting?
- Do you host events? Programs?
I think I saw you host before.
- I was a journalist.
- Meme, he was a journalist.
Ah, you were...
- You were broadcasting.
- Broadcasting, yes.
- Uh...
- On TV?
It's a school press conference,
so there are levels.
I went to nationals.
NSPC.
- That's what they call it.
- [AUDIENCE CHEERS]
- You were like a newscaster?
- Yeah.
So you're not shy
about public speaking?
In front of a camera, I'm not,
since being shy isn't
an option in that field.
You're not shy even
in serious situations?
Yes.
But if it's for fun,
you turn shy.
Yes, I back away
if that's the case.
Ah, okay. Let's see--
- Is newscasting your dream?
- No, I just tried it.
I didn't expect that I'd pass.
Let's see how JM is
as a newscaster.
Let's pretend, JM, that...
Ah...
Imagine you're in Poblacion
and you've witnessed
three gay people fighting a man.
Something like that.
Pretend that it's us three
who's beating that man up.
That went viral, right?
That report on Poblacion.
- Yes.
Pretend that you'll report that
something like that
is happening.
How would you do it?
Where's JM's camera?
Okay, something chaotic needs
to be happening in the back.
Come and stand here, JM.
Right here.
- Here.
- [FYANG] Do your best.
Don't embarrass me.
I don't know what to do!
Let's pretend that
someone's fighting.
[TETAY] He's the boss.
Yeah, he's the bar owner.
The guy was carrying a piece
of wood with a nail on it.
We can't do that, can we?
- That's a wooden plank.
- Okay.
Isn't there a random citizen in
the background every time?
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
- Go there in the corner.
- I'll do that.
- Go wave in the corner.
- I don't want to sit down.
- [LAUGHING SFX]
- Your ideas are so corny.
- [LAUGHTER]
The bystanders passing around.
Then let's go here.
There we go.
Let's go here so there's
space in the middle to fight.
I really want
to start a fight here.
Okay.
One, two, three, go.
- Hey, that's enough.
- Breaking news.
Good evening,
Kapuso   and  Kapamilya.
As you can see behind me,
there are four people--
Isn't she beautiful? [CHUCKLES]
Anyway,
as you can see behind me,
we are witnessing a huge fight.
Let's move a little closer
to get the full view.
Let's interview this person.
I think he looks injured.
Hello? What's going on?
Can you tell us what
happened? Are you injured?
I'm hurt! I was just drinking--
We'll cut the camera's here.
This is JM Ibarra,
your youth reporter.
- Alyssa Valdez.
- [CHEERING]
You won't stop, will you?!
They really won't stop!
Let's move a little closer
to get the full view.
- This woman is... is--
- Hey, hey!
She looks like she needs
to go to the hospital.
How are you, miss?
- It's so chaotic here!
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Hold on the basin!
It might get ruined.
- [SCREAMS]
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
- The fish fell into the basin!
- [LAUGHTER]
This is getting dangerous,
so we'll cut the cameras.
This is JM Ibarra,
your youth reporter.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Yes!
[TETAY] That was great.
You did a good job.
Give that to me.
You might hit someone.
You did a good job.
Have you tried reporting
for  TV Patrol?
Don't they have a segment where
you can report celebrity news?
- Once.
- We've tried it, Meme.
- Oh, so you've tried it?
- Yes, one time.
Sounds like fun, right?
That's good. You have a fallback
if you get tired of tapings
you can move into
news reporting.
It kind of feels different now.
I don't think I can do
news reporting anymore.
That's great, they'll send you
off to do war coverage.
No, he might die.
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMS]
- [TETAY] Aw, she's concerned.
Ah!
Pretend you'll report on
JMFyang-- I mean, Fyang.
- What will you say?
- JMFyang!
- I like that.
- I forgot that was two people.
Pretend you'll report on a young
lady named Fyang Smith.
And that she's
so beautiful, oh wow.
- [LAUGHS]
- Report it yourself!
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- Go, JM.
- [NEWS MUSIC PLAYING]
- Reporting again.
Good evening,
Kapamilya   and  Kapuso .
Right now,
we are currently with--
- For me,
- Pretend I'm not with you.
-This, I want to be with you.
-Okay, okay.
[AUDIENCE CHEERS]
You're not a fish,
but you always seem
to fish for compliments.
- [LAUGH TRACK PLAYING]
- And we are currently--
Your name should
be Fishing Smith.
Go.
We are currently with the
most beautiful woman I've seen.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
And we are here
with Fyang Smith.
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- Ah...
Fyang Smith,
I would like to ask--
No, I want to.
Pretend this is
a real interview,
Alright.
what would be
the million-dollar question
you'd ask her for
the very first time.
So, this is-- oh, he's thinking.
This wasn't part of his plan.
I don't have to think about this
- I just thought of it.
- Okay.
What's the
billion-dollar-question
you want to ask her
for the very first time?
I have a question
for you, Fyang Smith.
- What is it?
- And I just want the truth.
- Okay.
- Hopefully you answer it.
- When will you say yes to me?
- Oh!
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMS]
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't be too flirtatious.
The studio will stink!
The audience looks
like they need to pee!
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
You guys are crazy!
Yes, Fyang?
Would you like me
to answer you now?
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
[AUDIENCE] Yes! Yes!
[LAUGHTER]
Is it possible? [CHUCKLES]
You can't answer the question
with another question.
Oh.
What?
You can't answer the question
with another question.
It's like you're asking him too.
When will I answer you?
- [SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
If you'd pick a date--
just a number,
when will you say yes to him?
Yes, that's right.
Wow, taking advantage, Verna?
[VERNA] This is making
my heart flutter!
[LAUGHTER]
If I had to pick the date,
it would be one.
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- It's what?
- One.
So your date is on the first?
- [FYANG] One.
- [JM] Why one?
There's only one, right?
No, wait.
I'm a field reporter, right?
Usually, there are follow-up
questions. So why the first?
Why the first? It's because...
It's both our lucky number.
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Why--
What month, if ever?
January first.
Are you guys Fyang?
January first? That's New Year!
There are fireworks shooting.
[LAUGHTER]
- [TETAY] Jm, Fyang--
- So, after you say yes,
something
will immediately happen.
January first.
It's great because it's the
start of the year, right, guys?
- Yes!
Fine. January.
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- January?
- January one.
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I got distracted by the person
laughing in the front.
Her gums are
the only thing showing.
Could you laugh for us? Yes!
Don't cover your mouth!
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- [VERNA] She's shy.
- Wow.
-[TETAY] She seems happy.
Do you have any
questions for JM?
Um...
Your tattoo looks crazy,
it looks like you have
a band around your arm.
- Right?
- It's like a package tape.
- [LAUGHTER]
- What's you question?
Your question should be
something you haven't asked him.
[CHUCKLES]
Do you really want me
to be your future?
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
She's fishing again!
[LAUGHS]
[VERNA] Go, Fyang.
- Well?
- [JM] Uh...
Well...
I've told her so many times
that I'm willing to wait,
but when that day comes,
for me, that's it.
Do you get it?
- To me,
- He's asking
if you understood him
he probably
thinks you're stupid.
As if he's saying, "Are you
an idiot? Why don't you get it?"
- [TETA] He has a lot of medals!
- Yeah, yeah.
If people asked me that,
I'd get offended.
- [FYANG] Me too.
- Like, do you think I'm stupid?
It's like he thinks
so little of you.
- Wow, look at that hug.
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
He's being opportunistic.
Sometimes it feels
so good to play dumb
- just to be cuddled, right?
- [FYANG] Yes!
[TETAY] Oh, yes!
Are you like that too, Vince?
[LAUGHTER]
- My eldest son is big now.
- [LAUGHTER]
Vince probably has
bruises all over him now.
Verna even bit him!
[LAUGHTER]
That's crazy.
You've both asked questions
and both answered it,
but your fans have questions.
- Right?
- [TETAY] Oh, yeah!
Oh, you do something
like that too?
It's fun to connect with
your fans every once in a while.
- That's true.
- They might have questions.
Your fans might have
questions for you now!
So, who wants to ask
JM and Fyang a question?
- [TETAY] Raise your hand.
- Raise your hand.
- [VINCE] Raise your hand.
- [VICE] Pick one.
- Who has a question?
- I'll go for this girl!
Yes!
[TETAY] Hi!
What's your name?
Erika Bueno.
- Good day to you, Erika.
- Erika Bueno.
You look like you
lend people money.
[TETAY] What would
you like to ask?
This is for Fyang.
Everyone knows
that you are generous
to the people you love--
to JM and your family,
It's like the whole world
knows about that fact.
to the point that sometimes,
people think you're gay,
when you give gifts.
Do you have
a problem with that?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [TETAY] Let me handle this.
Your tone was off.
So what if she gives
gifts like that!
You know what--
Does giving gifts
mean that she's gay?
Can't she just be... generous?
- [LAUGHS]
- Generous.
Okay, going back
to your question.
Is it true that you gave
so many gifts to people?
JM a camera , shoes,
necklace,
and bracelet?
Oh, she's nosy!
She knows everything!
[TETAY] Okay, I'll admit it.
I gave it to JM.
I'm sorry.
Fyang, what can you say?
Um, I think you're overreacting
when you said I give too
many gifts like a gay person.
I've never given
you shoes, right?
I've never given him shoes.
Does giving him shoes
make you a gay person?
[TETAY] We're known
for giving rubber shoes!
It's just you! I've never
given anyone rubber shoes.
- [VINCE] I heard you gave--
- [TETAY] Never? Really, Meme?
I gave an Islander slippers
once. It was Islander slippers.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Slippers.
It was an entry level.
I heard you give out
motorcycles.
- What?
- Motorcycles.
I heard houses!
I give them water pumps.
Their water supply got
cut off. That's why.
There's this superstition that
if you give them a pair of shoes
- That they'll step on you?
- No, they'll leave you.
They'll leave you behind.
- You're generous with gifts?
- Yes, super.
- My family, friends, and JM.
- [TETAY] That's nice.
I gave him a bracelet,
and he lost it.
- Oh!
- What kind of bracelet is that?
- [JM] No, it was--
Ah, wait your turn.
[LAUGHTER]
Ah, it's a one-of-a-kind
bracelet.
- What is it?
- It's a unique bracelet.
- Is it a rock or--
- It is!
Why did you lose it?
She gave me accessories!
A necklace and--
Yes, because he doesn't
like to wear accessories
- so I bought him some.
- So I could get used to it.
It's not that expensive
because I didn't have
that much money back then.
I had an event in Davao,
and she gave me
the bracelet the day before.
I lost it the same day because
I'm not used to wearing it.
[VICE] Oh.
How do you feel if a woman
is generous towards you?
Do you feel
shy, turned off, belittled, not
used to it, or uncomfortable?
I'm just not used to it.
Fyang is generous even
if there's no occasion.
Like, sometimes she'll notice
that I play basketball a lot,
she gave me a tracker
to track my health.
She noticed that I was learning
video editing and vlogging,
she gave me an action camera.
That's not my action camera.
- You bought that.
- No, not that.
- The Gimbal.
- That's just cheap.
You gave it to me just because,
and that felt like a big deal.
- That's fine.
- Super.
Ion loves basketball equipment.
You bought him a ring?
I bought him an opponent to play
[LAUGHTER]
- It's hard playing alone!
- See?
So many people give
shoes, balls, ring.
I bought him
an opponent to play with.
I bought nine men.
Four men to be his team mates,
and the other five
would be their opponent.
I bought it for him.
[VERNA] You bought
people for him.
I bought him teammates
and his opponents.
But you know what,
I'm just happy that
generousity is being used
when describing gay people.
- Yeah.
- Right?
Being gay and generous
is a good thing.
[TETAY] I don't get offended
when people say that.
- Yes.
- Me too.
I don't like it when being gay
is attached to being abusive.
Right? Like being abusive
when it comes to being generous.
I don't think it's just us gays.
Whether you're a man
or a woman in love,
- you just...
- Yes.
[TETAY] When
you love something,
love doesn't come
with a price tag.
If it made you happy at
that time, then share it.
- You're happy.
- Yes.
And if that's
your love language--
I'll let you speak later
when it's needed.
I told you to fix the water
in there.
- Wash the dishes.
- Meme, I'm a co-host.
And don't give opinions
about love.
You haven't experienced it.
I'm kidding!
Yes. What are you saying
say about love, Verna?
Of course, when we talk
of love languages,
I'm also with Fyang on this.
I'm also big on gift-giving.
I hope you appreciate
and cherish it.
That's really her
love language: gift-giving.
- She used to be a reindeer.
- [LAUGHTER]
She's with Santa Claus.
What can you say about women
who are generous to men?
You know, for me,
it doesn't matter
whether you're gay,
man, or woman.
It's really up to that person.
And you'll feel
their sincerity in giving.
It feels great
to show appreciation
for those kinds of things,
gifts that are from the heart.
[VICE] Ooh. Okay.
And for sure
he didn't mean to lose it.
The next time
Fyang gifts him something,
JM will take care of it.
Son, you take care of it, okay?
It's Fyang's gift.
Is it the one you sold to me?
- Oh! [LAUGHS]
- Not here.
I knew it. He pawns stuff.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[VERNA] Buy and sell.
How about you? What's your--
If your language is gift-giving,
what's yours, JM?
- [VERNA] Really?
- Me...
He hasn't said anything.
You're not a part of it.
Is it words of affirmation?
Is it quality time?
Ah, you should answer it, Fyang.
He's not much of a words
of affirmation type of person,
but...
Even if he doesn't
do that often,
he still makes me feel all
of the love languages.
- Aw.
Acts of service.
Things like that.
Yes, acts of service,
quality time, physical touch.
- [VERNA GASPS]
- Gift-giving.
- Things like that.
- How's his service?
- Acts of service?
- Spa.
- [LAUGHTER]
- He massages you.
He scrubs you.
What does JM do
that you love the most?
What he does
that I love the most, uh...
When he's affectionate.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[TETAY] How does
he show affection?
How does he do it?
Pretend that you're
- on the phone.
- Since he's shy,
pretend that you're
JM and he is Fyang.
- Okay.
- Show affection to him.
Just make a phone call.
Pretend you're on the phone.
Pretend you're
on the phone, motherfucker!
Oh, sorry. Sorry, sorry.
I don't want
my daughter to wait.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I was carried away.
He's holding a phone now.
Phonetangina
(motherfuckingphone).
- [LAUGHTER]
- Phonetangina?
It's like the Fyang pun.
Fyanget.  (Fyang-ugly)
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
That's really funny!
Phonetangina  and  Fyanget.
[LAUGHS]
[TETAY]
Okay, he's on the phone now.
I'm just on my phone--
Hold on.
Pretend you're really Fyang.
Do her actual gestures.
How she is when she's on her
fyone. "Fyone"?  I mean phone.
Okay, just stay there.
He'll just do this.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- Like this.
- Does he kiss you?
Does he kiss me?
Do you kiss me?
I don't think so. We've
never gotten to that point.
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- We hug.
- Just hug.
- [VERNA] Just hug.
Even by accident,
you've never kissed?
- No.
- [AUDIENCE SHOUTING]
Liars are going to die, Fyang.
[LAUGHTER]
- See you got nervous!
- [VERNA LAUGHS]
He's more of a hugger.
Ah.
Physical touch, stuff like that.
Me too. I like hugging.
Hugs are something else.
It's a huge help
for one's mental health.
You need one hug a day.
They say it's seven.
- Why?
- Seven hugs a day.
Those 20-second hugs
are a big help.
- [TETAY] You like hugging.
- Yes.
They say hugs are almost
as good as words of affection.
Yes, hug me.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[TETAY] Hugs are done
with both hands, right?
Yes, it's 20 seconds.
Seven hugs a day?
I give more than that.
Right?
I'm aware that physical touch is
my top love language to give.
- Ah, so you're a top.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [LAUGHING SFX PLAYING]
- No, top to give!
He has a list, and physical
touch is on top of his list!
[TETAY] Being on top
is an act of service.
Hugging is
at the top of his list.
[VERNA] Next is--
[LAUGHTER]
She loves it
when the topic is like that.
[TETAY]
Yes, she's getting butterflies!
Do you hug him too?
Hugging is at the bottom
of my list.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- I meant least!
- [TETAY] What is this?!
Top!
- Right?
- She's right!
Hugging isn't at the top
of her list.
- [FYANG] No. It's the least.
- It's the least.
[AUDIENCE] He's blushing!
He's blushing!
- Are you having fun?
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
- Yes, it's fun.
- It's fun, right?
Your neck looks a bit red.
Why? Kiss his neck so--
[LAUGHTER]
[TETAY] She's down!
[SQUEALS]
- [VICE LAUGHS]
- I'll do it later
- when there are no cameras.
- Why are you blushing?
How do you feel?
Where is that reaction
coming from?
I don't know... I've always
been like this, Meme.
He's really shy, isn't he?
But people who get shy in public
are the ones
very expressive privately
to the person
they think is deserving,
uh...[TONGUE CLICKS]
of their love and attention.
That's it.
Who else would like
to ask a question?
- That girl right there!
- [TETAY] Verna, Vince, pick!
We have one over here.
He's blushing because
there's a mackerel there.
[CHUCKLES]
Hi, girl. What's your name?
I'm Myra.
Myra, what's your question?
Hi, good evening,
JM. Fyang, and Meme Vice.
[VICE]
Hello. Why are you in falsetto?
[LAUGHTER]
[IN SOFT VOICE] Hi, JM, Fyang...
My voice really sounds tiny.
It's okay. Verna's tiny
and she isn't even a voice.
- What's your question?
- Okay, I have a question
for the both of them.
[IN SOFT VOICE] What's your
question for the both of them?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [VICE] This is amazing.
Are you friends with Thumbelina?
Is it true that you fought
when you climbed Mt. Ulap?
There are some speculations
that you fought.
- [IN SOFT VOICE] Speculations.
- [LAUGHTER]
[IN SOFT VOICE] You need
to spit out your phlegm.
[VERNA] Did you hear
the question right?
- Yes.
- [VERNA] She has asthma.
[LAUGHTER]
What's the question again?
[IN SOFT VOICE] Is it true
that you fought in Mt. Ulap?
There are some speculations...
Oh my god!
Is it true that you fought
when you climbed Mt. Ulap?
[IN SOFT VOICE] Is it true that
you had an X-ray the other day?
- Yes.
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
You fought on Mt. Ulap?
What happened on Mt. Ulap?
Uh, no. Because it's...
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHTER]
Okay.
No, we didn't get
to climb Mt. Ulap
because it was closed that day
due to a storm.
But we didn't fight.
Just a little misunderstanding
- the night before.
- Why?
She did something that night.
What did you do?
- You say it.
- It's just a small thing.
I just told her off and...
Ah, he's like your father.
I thought you guys
were a love team.
No, it was--
I left home around 9PM.
I told him, "Hey, I'm just
going over to my friend's."
"Pick me up
and drop me off at home."
That's it.
The situation was,
he waited in the condo's lobby
for a long time.
He was texting me.
It was around 3 or 4AM.
He said he's already downstairs.
Then he kept calling
and I wasn't picking up.
Why?
- My friend was opening up.
- And--
And the guard
was asking me to leave.
We were already arguing.
Oh, so that's how you are.
When you're with your friends
and your boyfriend calls,
you won't answer.
Ouch.
- He's not my boyfriend yet.
- [VICE] What?
He's not my boyfriend yet.
Especially if it's your friend.
You asked him to pick you up.
You still won't answer the call?
But even--
You'd respond to the deliveries
at your house.
It's not that I wouldn't answer
at all. I texted him.
I didn't want him to hear
what my friend was sharing.
- You texted him, "Hold on..."
- I did.
She did. You're so dramatic.
No, she texted me she's
all good and to pick her up.
So I did. I was nearby.
Why did you text him that
when you're still talking?
- It's your fault.
- [CHUCKLES]
My friend suddenly opened up.
It was sudden.
You should've asked then.
Well, that's her friend,
not mine.
It's not his friend. Why did he
have to suffer in the lobby?
- You should've explained.
- I said sorry.
- [VERNA] She did say sorry.
- That was already late
and our trip
was early in the morning.
So yeah,
it was just a misunderstanding.
What don't you like about Fyang?
- There we go.
- None, I've accepted it all.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [ALL] Aw!
None. We've been together
long enough.
Which of her traits...
[CROWD CHEERING, LAUGHING]
Wow, you're acting
as if you even weigh 55kg.
[LAUGHTER]
Which of her traits
will make us say,
"Wow, he accepted that.
That's amazing."?
What intense trait of hers
is that,
but because of love,
you accepted it?
You said
you accepted her wholly.
I guess she's very,
uh...
she's very impulsive.
When she makes, uh...
like, a specific decision.
She didn't think of--
This was before.
She didn't think through whether
it would be good for her,
right or wrong.
It even got to a point
where her own mom
didn't like her decision.
Now my mom's in on this.
- I love you, Mother.
- No.
Just to emphasize the intensity.
You've shared that
with Vhong and me.
He said,
"Sometimes, Fyang can't control
the burst of her emotions."
He speaks Tagalog so deeply.
I remember he's from Quezon.
Yeah, he was like,
"Sometimes, Fyang can't control
the burst of her emotions.".
Wow.
What do you think people have
a hard time accepting about you
but he did?
Uh...
I think being...
huh?
- Are you stupid?
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[LAUGHTER]
What's the question again?
I'm sorry.
[LAUGHTER]
My trait that you've accepted
but others can't.
But, girl, admit it...
[LAUGHTER]
- You get brain farts.
- Yes.
[LAUGHTER]
That's it. You've accepted it
but others can't.
Yes, yes.
Uh, maybe most of the time,
from what I've read,
it's the way I talk.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's it.
They have a problem
with it so...
Your true self
that others don't like,
but JM accepts it regardless,
- and loves you even more.
- Yes.
That's what I liked about her.
[CROWD CHEERING]
But, girl, admit it...
[LAUGHTER]
That's really what love is.
That'll make you appreciate
the people who love you
even more.
Because a lot of us--
You'll notice it yourself.
There are things about yourself
that you don't even like.
But others choose to love
and embrace them.
And they will make you feel
that despite having that
or being this,
it's okay
and you are worthy of love.
[CROWD CHEERS]
I will not take that
against you.
And that will not make you
a lesser person.
Others choose to use that
against us,
but some choose to accept
and embrace it.
It's beautiful.
- Who else has a question?
- Thank you.
[VINCE] I have a question here
from Jaylord.
Jaylord.
[VICE] How can you tease him
when his name is Jaylord?
- [FYANG LAUGHS]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
What's your name, bro--
[VICE]
You guys kind of look alike.
- Jaylord really believed it.
- I'll stand next to you.
Here. Do you see it?
He's like my twin.
[VICE]
Yes, you have the same hair.
What's your question?
Hi, JM and Fyang.
- My question-- [CHUCKLES]
- [FYANG] That's not your voice.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Oh, you know him?
I know him.
- Why? What's his real voice?
- [JAYLORD LAUGHS]
You have the same voice
as the girl in pink?
- [LAUGHTER]
- No, Meme.
I heard it now. "No"
[LAUGHTER]
Okay, my question is,
who among your fellow actors
do you both get jealous of
when around each other?
- [VERNA] Ooh!
- [CROWD] Oh!
[VICE] I like that.
Okay.
Spill the tea.
You go first.
Or should I go first?
For me--
I shouldn't have asked.
For me, Meme,
personally, there's no one.
- No one.
- Even before?
Because he doesn't do anything
that'd make me jealous.
[CROWD] Ooh!
He never really
made me feel that...
her woman co-star is someone
I should be jealous of.
That's it.
- So I never--
- But sometimes...
[CROWD TALKING LOUDLY]
Even though they're not doing--
Motherfucker, hold on.
You're too loud!
Do you want to be
the guests instead?
[TETAY]
Meme, they just got excited!
I lost my train of thought
because you're too loud!
[TETAY] Hold on! Calm down!
I have a lot in mind!
I'm thinking about them,
I'm thinking of this--
- Motherfuckers!
- [LAUGHTER]
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- [TETAY] Calm down.
- I was carried away.
- [TETAY] They're our neighbors.
Sorry, I have an anger
management problem, I'm sorry.
Yes, I haven't been able
to go to therapy for 3 weeks.
- Please forgive me.
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
These are the kinds
of audiences here on  GGV
that are happy
when they're being cussed out.
- "Yay, Vice is cussing me!"
- [LAUGHTER]
[VICE LAUGHING]
They're happy
with me cussing them out.
- We love you, Meme!
I love you too.
Sometimes, your partner isn't
even doing anything,
and they don't make you doubt,
but there's that feeling--
It's normal to feel something
that's like, "Hmm..."
You didn't feel that ever?
The thing is I'm also pretty.
- [ALL CHEERING]
- I like it!
- It's all about security.
- Right?
- Secured
- That's it.
I'm pretty, Meme.
I can't do anything about it.
Well, then I'm sorry.
I felt that because I wasn't.
- Sorry.
- [FYANG] No.
Fyang kept repeating it to you.
"I'm pretty, Meme."
I'm sorry.
I won't let them air this.
[LAUGHTER]
No one will see this!
- No, it's the security.
- [TETAY] Right.
That's true.
I get jealous sometimes
because I have insecurities.
- [TETAY] Huh?
- Yes, I have insecurities.
Especially when people
say it over and over.
"He'll leave you eventually
because you're gay."
"He'll leave you
for some woman."
They weren't really doing
anything bad,
That's why we shouldn't read
and listen to that hate.
Until you just feel, "Huh? No."
I don't believe them.
That won't happen because one,
I'm not replaceable.
Secondly,
my partner isn't like that.
- [CHEERING]
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
That's true.
You're pretty
and JM isn't that kind of guy.
I also have insecurities, Vice.
But he doesn't love me
any less because of them.
So I feel very secure with him.
I have no reason
to get jealous.
I really don't.
- [VICE] Yeah. That's good.
- [AUDIENCE CHEERS]
[VICE] What about you, JM?
I'm a handsome guy, huh?
[LAUGHS]
- [AUDIENCE SHOUTS]
- [SILLY SFX]
- [JM CHUCKLES]
- Do you have any insecurities
about your relationship
with Fyang?
Oh, I heard there was a time
you got jealous of Darren.
- Darren?
- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
No. I mean...
What happened was...
[CHUCKLES]
We had an event in Dubai.
- [VICE] Okay.
- I wasn't jealous of Darren.
- Most of the time--
- Were you jealous of the camel?
Not Darren?
I feel jealous when she
gives other people attention.
I don't get jealous
of the person,
but of the attention
they receive.
- In that way.
- [VICE] They were having fun...
- ...without you.
- Yeah, I felt left out.
You were jealous?
- Not of Darren--
- Don't you want to know!
I don't like it when
she forgets about me.
- Ah...
- Mm-hmm.
I want her attention
at all times.
- [AUDIENCE GUSHING]
- [VICE] Wow.
- He's selfish.
- Possessive.
- Wow!
- [JM CHUCKLES]
We have given your fans
a chance to ask questions.
- [TETAY] Yes.
- Okay.
They asked nice questions.
Like I said, people say
negative things about us.
And you, Fyang,
are always a hot topic online.
Exactly, Vice!
Anything I say is
used against me.
Actually, I love it
when they turn on you.
- [FYANG] Why?
- I go, "Yes, I get a break."
[LAUGHTER]
- [TETAY] They forget about you.
- Yes.
And when they
turn on me again,
I wonder, "Where's Fyang?
What will she do next?"
I would tell
my social media team,
"Find an old video of Fyang.
Make it resurface."
But I love you.
We're in this together.
We sure are!
- We share the market.
- We love that.
- Let's share the market!
- [FYANG LAUGHS]
- Let's piss off the trolls!
- Yes!
Screw you all!
[LAUGHTER]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
But you know,
somehow, I have to
give it to the bashers.
Thank you for what
you've done for   GGV.
Our ratings are high
because the bashers and
supporters united for the show.
- [FYANG] Yes.
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Thank you very much
for coming together.
- Keep it up.
- Yes, stay united.
Keep watching together.
Keep talking about us.
But here, let's see
how you will react
to the not-so-beautiful
comments about you online
or whatever your bashers
are saying.
You are often criticized
for your behavior and actions.
Yes.
[VICE]
They say you lack...
- [TETAY] Finesse?
- They say you're blunt.
- Mm-hmm.
- That you lack media training.
They say you need training
in responding to questions.
- [VINCE] Aggressive.
- Stuff like that.
But you're different.
You're not the
typical sweet actress.
You're not
that kind of celebrity.
People label you as rude.
They say, "You know what,
she's so crass."
- [FYANG] Yes.
- That's the word.
So, let's see how you respond
to the hate tweets
or the not-so-beautiful tweets
about you
in a sweet way.
Okay, okay.
Because they say you're blunt.
I want to hear you respond
to hate tweets
- in the sweetest way possible.
- Okay.
But I don't want you
to be stressed.
- Holding it in is stressful.
- Mm-hmm.
We'll give you something
to help you with that.
Verna, please bring out
our gift.
- Oh, what's that?
- Squishy.
Squish your stress away.
- Wow, it's cute.
- [VICE] Oh, it's really nice.
Oh, this is fun.
It's cute. Oh!
- It's a soft ball.
- This one too. It's soft!
When's the last time
you held something like this?
[FYANG LAUGHS]
- [LAUGHTER]
- Just now.
Oh, just now?
I've seen these in bathtubs.
- [TETAY] Yes.
- We don't have one, Vice.
- Okay. [CHUCKLES]
- [TETAY LAUGHS]
Here's your squishy.
While you answer-- Oh.
Does it have glitter?
Just squish that one.
Okay, this is the first comment.
Geng Gang?
Did you gather the
unpleasant comments I asked for?
Please read them for Fyang.
Or...
Okay. Flash them on the screen.
Then read them to Fyang.
Let's hear
what they have to say.
Fyang, listen carefully.
"Fyang is so trashy."
- Um...
- Respond to that...
...in the sweetest way possible.
[TETAY] Maybe it's the way
she said, "Fyang is so trashy."
Okay. Trashy?
Like someone from the streets.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Uh, I think
it's not really trashy.
I think I'm just being...
[CROWD CHUCKLING]
...expressive.
I'm a very expressive talker.
I'm expressive in the things
I like to do.
And maybe
they just have these ideas
and stereotypes about actors.
That when you're an actress,
you have to be demure.
[CROWD CHEERS, CHUCKLES]
[VICE] Would you like to
give a message to the person
who posted that?
What would you like to tell
that person?
Okay, here's your camera.
I'm not trashy.
How demure!
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
I'm not trashy.
If you see me
in person, let's see.
[SNICKERS]
Give me that squishy.
Answer it like how Fyang would.
Is that so? [LAUGHS]
- [LAUGHTER]
- [TETAY] There we go!
- That's Fyang!
- They said you're trashy!
The man beside me loves me!
Does someone even love you?
[APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[TETAY] Boom!
What you're saying is,
"I may be trashy,
but someone loves me."
"You're not trashy,
but you're all alone!"
[SHOUTING]
Whoa!
Next, Vince. What's next?
Give me something intense.
[VINCE] Here it is.
Deliver it with conviction.
"Whatever she does,
she'll always be ill-mannered."
- [TETAY] Oh!
- [CROWD EXCLAIMS]
Gosh, they say
you're ill-mannered.
- But you have to be sweet.
- Okay.
How do you comment on that?
Uh, I'm not ill-mannered.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Yeah.
I think it's just that...
Um...
Can you help me?
Can you help me answer that?
Am I ill-mannered?
- Uh, I think not.
- Yeah.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
I'm not ill-mannered, right?
- They're talking cute.
- Yeah.
And so what if I'm ill-mannered?
I'm a nice person.
I'm not stepping on anyone.
It's just that... [SIGHS]
- Can you help me again?
- [LAUGHTER]
Give me the squishy.
Respond to that.
- Me?
- Yes, you're ill-mannered.
Oh, come on. No way!
Excuse me.
If I'm really ill-mannered
I should have slapped you.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- Right? I don't know.
- [TETAY] Yes!
[APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
[TETAY]
Her tone was milder this time.
But the mere fact that you
haven't been slapped. [LAUGHS]
Only proves
I'm not ill-mannered.
And the mere fact that
I hadn't fought with anyone...
- I'm not ill-mannered.
- Yes.
And remember,
there's cash in trash!
- Yes!
I have money!
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Tell them you have money
and they're trash!
[LAUGHTER]
- Are you happy with her answer?
- Yes.
- You are?
[CHUCKLES, LAUGHTER]
[VICE]
Was her mild tone convincing?
[TETAY] She was kind of
struggling with the sweet voice.
[IN SWEET VOICE]
"You know what..."
But you could see
her anger rising.
- [VICE] It didn't match.
- It didn't match the vibe.
What she's showing
is what she really feels.
[VERNA] Out of 10,
her sweetness is barely a 2.
- It's not convincing enough.
- [TETAY] It's more like a 1.
- You think it's a 1?
- Yeah.
[VINCE] I'm not satisfied yet.
It's better to be blunt
than to be fake.
- That's right.
- That's so cringe.
It's better to be authentic
than to hide your true self
deep inside.
[EXCLAIMING]
Give her a good one, Verna.
Go!
[TETAY IN SWEET VOICE]
Read it, Verna.
"What a combo. Stupid,
talentless, and impolite."
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
That's so rude.
You tweeted that, didn't you?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Does it sound like me?
[LAUGHS]
No, I love Fyang.
Okay. A sweet answer, please.
I think for the "stupid" remark,
yeah, I know.
- Sometimes, I am.
- [LAUGHTER]
I'm not going to deny it.
I have my fair share
of brain farts.
Because sometimes
I don't get enough sleep.
I can get really busy with work,
you know.
And for the "talentless,"
no, I'm not talentless.
I can dance.
- [CROWD CHEERS]
- Um...
[CROWD] Dance right now!
Hmm?
Let her finish, please.
Yeah. Can you please--
That's so ill-mannered
of you guys.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICE LAUGHING]
[VICE] Okay, go on.
I'm not talentless.
I can dance.
I can act.
You can ask Ms. Dina Bonnevie.
- And...
- Did you say act?
It sounds like
you're saying "ack."
- Yeah.
- [CHUCKLES]
- How stupid.
- Get your  ack  together.
What about impolite?
They said you're impolite?
Um...
I can say sometimes...
[VICE] You're rude sometimes?
No, I don't...
I don't think so.
I'm a nice,
well-moisturized girl.
- So, I'm not...
- Yeah?
Give me your squishy.
- Respond to that, Fyang.
- Okay.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [VERNA] Buckle up.
Yes, I'm not so smart
all the time.
We're not perfect here,
am I right?
The one who left that comment
is probably stupid too.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
I mean...
just look at their tweet.
The "Hahaha" is so tacky.
They're not happy because
the comment's not in all-caps.
"Talentless."
No, I'm not talentless.
I can dance.
I even have an album. Hello?
- [APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
- [FYANG LAUGHS]
[TETAY]
How about you being "impolite"?
With "impolite,"
I am sometimes.
But only when dealing
with these kinds of people.
- Ooh!
- [TETAY] Ooh! They deserve it.
You're more relaxed
when you let it out.
- Yes, it's...
- [VICE] It's heavy when...
Yes, and it's not really--
When I'm being sassy--
I can say
that I can get sassy sometimes.
But I'm only sassy towards
people who have done me wrong,
I think those are the people
who have done something to me
and they deserve
that sassy side of me.
Yes.
I don't want people to think
they can bully me.
So I think I have to show
that I can also push back.
- To put them in their place.
- Yes.
So they don't take
advantage of you.
You happy with her answers?
- Do you feel proud?
- Yes, very.
I want her to answer it
as she normally would.
How Fyang would really respond.
[TETAY IN SWEET VOICE]
You don't like her sweet vibe?
Like, "Gee, I'm so close
to smacking this person's head."
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
You don't like that?
[VICE IN CUTE VOICE]
JM, don't be mad.
I stabbed someone yesterday.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
What?
[IN CUTE VOICE]
They were messing with me!
[TETAY] That's how a girl
acts to get your attention.
What's the meanest comment
you've read about yourself?
- [JM] About me?
- What was the meanest thing
someone said about you?
I don't really read
comments about myself.
But most of the time
I get judged for
being quiet and
for having a blank expression.
[VICE] People were
bashing you the other day.
- About your  ASAP  performance.
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
[FYANG] See?
[CHUCKLES]
I asked Fyang about
that performance the day after.
You two were singing, right?
What did you say to me?
I said, "Vice, look at
the comments online!"
"I was giving everything
and JM was giving nothing."
[VICE] And remember
what you said after?
You said, "JM's acting
like he's still a virgin!"
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Remember?
We were laughing so hard.
She even said,
"I was getting close
and everything,
but he's playing hard to get
like some virgin!"
- [LAUGHTER]
- [FYANG] No!
But... Explain yourself.
[LAUGHING]
- Why did you act that way?
- No.
- Uh...
- Are you not a virgin?
- [VERNA] No?
- I mean--
I don't know
anything about that!
- Hmm?
- I have no idea!
[VICE LAUGHS]
No, um... [STAMMERS]
- Eh-eh-eh.
- No, I admit it.
I'm not that expressive.
- You're not the showy type.
- I'm not good at fan service.
I don't do it
during performances.
I didn't know they gave her...
- Different instructions.
- For the performance.
I was introduced
as a leading man,
so I had to maintain
this matinee idol image.
So that's what
I was keeping in mind.
The problem was,
she didn't know about it.
- And I--
- Then she got so close.
Yes.
What were you two singing?
- Ligaya.
The song was  Ligaya
but you didn't look happy.
Only Fyang looked happy.
Were you trying to kiss him?
You were really close to him.
- [FYANG] No!
- You were holding him tightly.
But I was briefed that
we should act very sweet.
"Show your sweet side.
Really lean in to him."
And every time she moved close,
you moved away from her.
[JM] She was so close
to my face then
that if I turned around,
I would've kissed her.
Why didn't you?
Her manager would get mad.
So... [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
[VICE]
She would've defended you.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
If your manager scolded you
for kissing JM,
what would you say?
[LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- Huh?
[LAUGHS]
[VICE LAUGHING]
What a flirt.
That's her character
in their movie.
- She wasn't acting.
- [FYANG CLAPS]
[FYANG] Oh!
By the way, Vice!
He's been practicing
this dance.
- What dance?
- The one that's trending.
- The one that goes like this.
- No!
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
- Show them!
- Come on!
- Show us!
- Don't leave us hanging!
- Yes!
- Can he do it?
- He can!
- He can dance it?
- He memorized the steps!
- Will he get applauded there?
- He'll get applauded there!
Let's do it, JM.
[CHANTING] JM! JM! JM!
So we can use that
for a ballad song
- and then do those steps?
- Yes! Yes!
- Okay, JM...
- Go! You can do it!
- Center stage, please.
- There you go!
It's hot, take off your jacket.
You'll get hot and sweaty there.
[ALLURING MUSIC PLAYING]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
- [FYANG] Come on!
- [JM] Help me.
Okay, I'll help you. Come here.
[ALLURING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[VICE CHUCKLES]
It's funny.
It's like they're
each other's talent.
Now you're like JM's manager.
"Hurry, there are
producers here. Dance."
[LAUGHING]
- He might get discovered.
- You might get discovered.
You really support
each other, huh?
That's great. Let's give them
a round of applause.
- [APPLAUDING]
- JM and Fyang!
[LAUGHS]
When you push each other,
you have no choice
but to do it, right?
You don't want
to embarrass each other.
Yes! Besides, Meme,
if he gets embarrassed,
I'll get embarrassed too.
- [VICE LAUGHS]
- Right?
Why do you keep
practicing that dance?
I don't. I just keep seeing it
over and over.
[VICE] What? Every taping?
Even when we're at the taping,
he really practices it.
You know, people with
quiet personalities like that
are usually the ones
with a wild side.
- [TETAY] That's true.
- [VERNA] That's true, Meme.
- That's true!
- In the bathroom,
in front of the mirror.
The guy dancing in the video
is really good.
They're perfectly in sync.
And the steps are really good,
so I'm copying them.
- What are the steps again?
- Come on,
- just show us the full steps.
- The whole steps.
- Yes.
- Come on, don't be shy.
Go ahead.
- [TETAY] What?
- [CHANTING] One more! One more!
- Say what?!
- Go!
- [TETAY] Boss JM!
Welcome to... [INAUDIBLE]
Come on, show us.
Pretend you're teaching
Tetay the steps.
So there's a purpose.
Tetay, he's going to teach you.
Tetay used to be an Adonis.
But she got gout,
so she just became gay instead.
[LAUGHING]
JM, I'll be watching you.
You have to copy his steps.
- You have to learn them.
- I'll hold your mic.
Why does he need a mic
if he's going to dance?
How is he going
to teach her, Meme?
- Is he just going to dance?
- Yes, even just a little.
You need to get the steps.
Go.
[ALLURING MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, open your legs.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
- [ALLURING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[VICE] Wow, your uncle
is so talented.
- [LAUGHING]
- [LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, he's really good
at coaching. I got it.
And he's actually
a really good dancer too.
- Right?
- I think you can do that too.
- I'm not a dancer, okay?
- I think so, too.
But what she's going to dance--
- [CHANTING] Vice Ganda!
- Oh...
[CHANTING] Vice Ganda!
Vice Ganda! Vice Ganda!
- [ALLURING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[TETAY] Vince said
you're doing it wrong, Meme.
- Oh, then show me how.
- Vince will show you how.
Show us, Vince.
[ALLURING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[VICE] Oh!
The flooring got a hole in it.
- [LAUGHING]
- [LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING]
Amazing!
JM, thank you.
Oh no, they're drooling
while JM is dancing.
[LAUGHING]
[TETAY] Do the wiping again.
Okay. Will our jaws drop at
this love team's revelations?
Let's start Deep Truth!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Here in Deep Truth,
each guest will reveal
a deep statement.
Through questioning
and analyzing,
Geng Gang,
Verna and Tetay, and I,
have to guess
if the deep statement
is trot (truth) or charot (lie).
Whoever gets the wrong guess
or judgment
will face
a deep punishment later.
Okay. Let's go to JM.
Bring in the statements
the guests will reveal.
Why did you get a squishy?
[LAUGHS]
- Is this stressing you out?
- No.
This is it, the deep truth.
Okay, so JM's turn first. JM.
Give that to me first.
JM will stand up.
You'll show
and read it to everyone.
JM...
What is your deep statement?
"I confronted a director
who disrespected Fyang."
[CROWD] Ooh.
Confronted?
Like you called them out
and told them off?
Mm-hmm.
Confronted them like,
"Director, hold on."
Was it a bit aggressive?
Yes. Uh, I was away and then...
So you went there
just to confront him?
Mm-hmm.
You weren't in the scenario,
but when you found out,
you confronted the director--
Yes, I wasn't there.
How did he disrespect her?
Uh...
You know, the usual case
of men disrespecting women.
Like, indirectly telling her
that she's delectable.
- Did he wear her panties?
- [CHUCKLES]
Did he try on her bra?
It didn't fit.
The director told her...
"You're delectable."
Ooh.
The director told me
I'm delectable.
But it was indirect like...
Confronted...
How did you confront him?
Like you barged right
into the set and then,
- "Director, yada yada!" or...
- No.
Or you asked
to talk to the director.
[TETAY] Okay,
let's say I'm the director.
How did you confront him?
What happened?
So, I went to the set, and--
Well, of course, we have
to lead with kindness first.
Oh, did you have
a prayer meeting first?
- Yes.
- [LAUGHING]
"Since we're in
a prayer meeting,
Director, please share
what you did earlier.
Then we'll pray over you."
There's also a feeding program.
"I'll get mad at you later.
Eat first."
Kindness comes first.
Let's have a feeding program.
I went to see Fyang
in the dressing room.
Because I haven't met
the director yet.
And I couldn't tell
who the director was
because he's not that old.
Almost everyone in set was...
- Oh, so he's young.
- [JM] Mm-hmm.
Around my age.
And then I asked Fyang
who was it.
- Is he from ABS-CBN?
- No.
Oh, good.
He'll be fired if he is.
When you confronted
the director,
did he answer you angrily?
Yes, definitely.
I didn't want it to come
from me first,
so Fyang talked to him first.
And as their conversation
went on,
his voice kept getting louder.
Then he denied it so much
that you could tell
he really did disrespect her.
[TETAY] So the director's voice
kept getting louder?
- Yes.
- Oh, so he's quite the belter.
- Oh...
- Who's that director?
"You're so delectable!"
His voice is getting higher.
Is he a man?
- Yes, he's a man. A big one.
- His voice is getting higher?
What do you think?
A lot of people saw it?
Her team.
- Oh...
- Fyang's team.
Because I let them
into the dressing room.
If the question
is whether JM can do it,
I think he can.
Hmm. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I'm sure he can.
Yeah, I think so too.
But do you think
he'd really do it?
That's what we want to know,
Kapuso   and   Kapamilya.
You're on the nose line too,
right?
- Not much.
- You should've put more on.
I asked her for a little.
[VERNA] Actually, even Vince
has a nose line.
- Hmm...
- I feel like...
Maybe he's capable of doing it,
but I don't think
he'd go that far just to do it.
I mean, even when
JM was still little,
I was already the
one taking care of that kid.
He's really obedient.
If you tell him, "Do not touch,"
he really won't touch it.
If you tell him, "Do not fight,"
he really won't fight.
If you tell him, "Kiss Mama,"
he'll kiss Mama.
Kiss Mama. [LAUGHS]
Just kidding.
You're a man, and your
girlfriend was disrespected,
someone told her,
"You're so delectable,"
and you wouldn't confront him
even though you're new
to the industry?
Uh...
I would confront him, but...
in a way that
I wouldn't make a scene.
Because if I make a scene,
then it would be like--
[VICE] So how would you
confront him?
I'd just be more aggressive
in a way...
When you get to the set,
"Director!
I had catering brought here.
Come on, let's talk.
The two of us will eat."
Maybe...
I'd approach him right away
and directly ask him
if it's true that he did that.
Oh, what if he raises his voice?
Oh, I can't match someone
when it comes to fighting.
What if he says,
"Yes, I said that.
What's your problem?"
- [VERNA] Oh...
- [TETAY] There!
What then? Would you fight back?
Yes, I told her
she's delectable.
I'm the director here, so what?!
Yes, I'd fight back.
- Why?
- [CROWD] Ooh!
- You're so delectable.
- [LAUGHING]
- At least he admitted it.
- So he's the delectable one.
What is it really?
She's just used
to being attacked.
Where they're from, Meme,
she's the one who gets attacked.
- Why would I be attacked?
- They're carrying torches.
"Burn the witch!"
- [LAUGHING]
- I'm being tied up.
You look so good roasted!
- [LAUGHING]
- Just kidding.
- For me, it's a  charot.
- [VICE] It's  charot  for you.
-  Charot   also.
-  Charot  also.
He's too smart to do
something like that.
Maybe he could
cool things down first.
But he's from Quezon,
so he's a tough guy.
- [VERNA] Yes.
- People from Quezon,
the Batanguenos.
Aren't they the manly ones?
That's why you really
like him, right?
You feel like
he'll defend you, right?
For me...
- Trot.
- I'm  charot.
I'm   trot.
Can you repeat your statement?
"I confronted a director
who disrespected Fyang."
I say it's  trot,
they say it's  charot.
So what is the deep truth?
Trot   or  Charot?
[AUDIENCE SHOUTS]
[TETAY] What is it?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Should I say it?
It's  trot.
Oh!
When was this? Was it recent?
[FYANG]
Yes, it happened recently.
Is it a TV series or a movie?
Um, I think...
Uh...
It's not a TV series,
it's not a movie.
Content shoot.
I did a content shoot.
And then,
it got to a point where
I was wearing something short.
I was wearing a tube,
stuff like that.
I was uncomfortable
from the beginning.
I was really uncomfortable
because he kept on talking.
But of course, he's a director,
I was being respectful.
Then I felt disrespected.
My makeup artist's assistant
told me,
"The director said
you look delectable."
- [TETAY] Oh my god.
- Hmm.
Then I texted him.
"Daniel, I feel disrespected..."
- Who's Daniel?
- Him.
- [VICE] Ah...
- [CROWD LAUGHING]
Turns out it wasn't me.
[VERNA] It wasn't him.
So you texted him...
"Daniel, the director
disrespected me."
I'm not the type who...
I can't always
defend myself alone.
It depends.
It's a man so I'm worried
he'd punch me.
I'd be knocked out.
So I told him.
It hadn't even been 30 minutes,
and he was already at ABS-CBN.
He had come from
so far away back then.
I forgot where he was,
but he was really far away.
When he entered the room--
I'll demonstrate it.
I was in the dressing room.
Action, action.
And then the director's here.
JM came in.
He was here
and that's the dressing room.
He came into my dressing room.
He asked,
"Which one is the director?"
And I said,
"The man wearing glasses."
And then, he was like,
"Hey, you, come here. Get in."
- Oh!
- Like that!
Because the director
is still young?
No, he already looks old.
- Ah...
- But he's actually young.
I don't know. Then he said...
"Come here. Get in."
The director said, "Me?"
He said, "Yeah, you.
Come here, get in."
That's really how he does it.
"What did you say about Fyang?"
"I didn't say anything
to Fyang."
I left the dressing room
because I was scared
he'd punch him.
So you just left him
to fend for himself?
- [LAUGHING]
- Amazing!
And then you even texted him,
"Daniel, I'll get going.
You can handle it."
- "You're old enough."
- [FYANG] Yes.
No, I was going
to get dressed too, Meme,
since I was still at work.
So I got changed.
Then, he called for me.
He wants me to come inside.
He was really pissed.
He said,
"What did he do to you?"
And I called
my makeup artist's assistant.
I said, "What did you hear?
What did he say?"
"He said you look delectable."
I told him,
"Why did you say that?"
"Why did you say that?" I asked.
He said,
"What? I didn't say that."
I said, "Don't lie.
I will slap you."
- Ooh.
- [FYANG] That's it.
When she stepped up,
she felt bigger than me.
- Yes.
- I just stood there.
[LAUGHING]
She suddenly became a C cup.
She just suddenly became
a C cup when she got mad.
Oh! What happened
to the director?
He was being so defensive.
His voice kept getting louder.
I was already ready
to argue back.
Then when it was
my turn to talk,
just as I was about to
approach them, I was surprised
when someone started
singing  "Happy Birthday"
outside the dressing room.
When I went out, it was the
managers from Star Magic.
- It was my birthday too.
- [VICE] So it was a prank?
- No, it's not!
- It's not a prank. It's like--
[VICE] Why did somebody
sing "Happy Birthday?"
[FYANG] It was his birthday!
I was smiling like this,
and thanked them.
[LAUGHS]
[VICE] Is everyone
in Star Magic okay?
You sang "Happy Birthday" in the
middle of a tense situation?
- [FYANG] It's them! Over there.
- They sang 'Happy Birthday."
I think someone should check
on these Star Magic people.
They were about to fight,
and you sang "Happy Birthday?"
Did they bring a cake?
- They brought two cakes.
- There's a video of that.
So, you didn't push through
with the fight?
- [LAUGHS] No.
- That's too bad!
The fight was stopped
because of your birthday!
[FYANG] It's those
people over there
[VICE] That would've
made the headlines!
If that ended up on the news,
I wouldn't have
been bashed that month.
[JM LAUGHS]
- My goodness.
- So, that's it?
So, you're not going to work
with that director ever again?
Yes, I really told my team,
if he'll direct something,
he better not
show his face to me.
I don't know what I'd do to him.
- [VICE] Does management know?
- They don't.
- They're only finding out now.
- That's right.
You should tell them,
so he'd get banned.
- [JM] Yes.
- [FYANG] Right.
No one should be subjected
to that kind of environment.
- True.
- Yes.
Right?
That's also one of the reasons
why I stopped wearing
revealing clothes.
That's why
you're wearing pants?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- But look at your top.
It's the other way around now.
Good job. I understand
your thought process now.
- [FYANG] Right?
- Yes.
- Mindset.
- But admit it, Fyang.
[LAUGHS]
No, but like what
we usually say...
...women shouldn't just let
those instances slide.
Like wearing something revealing
doesn't give others
the right to be a pervert.
- That director deserved it.
- Yes.
He should treat
everyone with respect.
- I commend you for that.
- Me too.
- Yes.
- That's also--
For me, it's just that
I can't always protect her
from all the bashing
on social media
because I'm also not used to it.
[VICE] Yes, it doesn't
have to be always,
but there are times that
you have to show up for her.
- That's more serious.
- You stepped up for her.
That's a  kilig
(affection) point.
- Yes, girl. Definitely.
- [APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
[VICE] That's really
sweet of him.
Girl, admit it...
[LAUGHTER]
[VICE] True! That's great.
You guys are wrong.
Sorry, but at least...
We're wrong again.
[VICE] It's Fyang's turn.
Fyang, it's your turn.
- Okay.
- Stand up.
Fyang, what's
your deep statement?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
"In an event,
a woman invited JM"
"to go upstairs
to a room with her."
[CROWD EXCLAIMING] Ooh!
[CROWD EXCLAIMING INTENSIFIES]
[VICE] It's her statement,
but I saw your face.
You're the one
who looks nervous.
Your eyes glistened.
You're nervous,
like you're about to cry.
Of course. [NERVOUSLY LAUGHS]
[CROWD CONTINUES EXCLAIMING]
[VICE] So in an event,
a woman invited JM
up to her room?
Oh my god.
So...
Question.
- Where is it?
- Over here.
What event was this?
- Ball?
- Ball.
Our first ball together,
our first ball.
[CROWD CONTINUES EXCLAIMING]
- [TETAY] Ball...
- Was I there?
- I think no?
- [VICE] If no...
...then it's probably
a Star Magic event.
- Yes!
- Oh...
Was Vice there?
- She's everywhere.
- You weren't there.
Good thing I didn't
get involved in that issue.
[LAUGHING SFX]
You weren't there.
- Is she also a celebrity?
- She is.
- [VICE] Oh my gosh. Ah!
- [AUDIENCE SHOUTS]
So you found out about it?
- She invited JM upstairs...
- Mm-hmm.
...and you found out?
I found out
because he told me.
- Whoa!
- Wow!
- Slay!
- [VERNA] Pretty!
Oh, look at her.
[AUDIENCE MEMBER]
She's that girl!
[FYANG] You know it.
Did you see that girl there?
- Of course.
- So you know her?
I do know her.
- Until now?
- [VERNA] Oh!
Yeah. Until now.
She knows that there's
something between you and JM?
Why did she invite him
up to her room, then?
Um... For a drink.
- Oh!
- Wow!
[VICE] Did she know there's
something between you and JM?
I think...
Uh...
[VICE] Did she invite you?
- No.
- Ah, she had other plans.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
[TETAY] There's a hidden agenda
behind that drink.
- [VERNA] Exactly.
- [FYANG] She was like...
"Let's have an after-party
in my room."
- But you weren't invited?
- Yes.
- Ah...
- How suspicious.
Are you close with this girl?
- No?
- No.
- How'd she send you a message?
- No, um...
- I was on my way up--
- Why do you have her number?
- [VERNA] Yeah.
- No, she said it in person.
Ah, she did it in person?
She said, "Go up to my room"?
[JM] Yes.
I was heading up to my room.
And...
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
[FYANG] Don't be nervous.
I got you.
[CHEERING, SHOUTING]
She got you, dude!
- That's my daughter.
- Right?
[TETAY] So, she
invited you to her room,
then you told Fyang about it?
Mhm-hmm. I was in the
elevator when that happened.
Is she your age
or a little older?
Um... I think...
[AUDIENCE CLAMORING]
- Yes, she's older than me.
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[VERNA] Hmm...
Did you confront her?
No, because I'm not trashy.
- Yes!
- Ah! I like it!
So, she's a little
older than you.
Is she sexy?
- [CROWD EXCLAIMING]
- You know her?
- Seriously?
-[VICE] You know who it is?
- Did you go to her room?
- [LAUGHS]
- But did you go up?
- No!
- Why not? Come on!
- [VERNA] Yeah.
[COMEDIC SFX]
- She's not the jealous type.
- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
- You didn't go to her room?
- I didn't.
How did you feel
about her invitation?
I was tired, because
I just got out of  PBB.
We were in the elevator,
and I didn't know
which floor we were in.
I just said hello to her.
I even bowed when I greeted her,
because I knew who she was.
[LAUGHS]
- She's an actress.
- Is she Japanese?
- She's Japanese?
- You bowed to her?
And then, that happened.
Did you decline her
invitation to go up to her room?
[JM] I just smiled.
I didn't want to
disrespect her or something.
- [TETAY] You just smiled back?
- Mm-hmm.
- You didn't respond?
- She was speaking in English.
- She's quite posh.
- [VERNA] Oh...
- Ah...
- Really?
[AUDIENCE CLAMORING, SHOUTING]
Oh my gosh.
Is she from ABS-CBN
or was she invited to the event?
- She's from ABS-CBN.
- Oh!
[AUDIENCE SHOUTING]
That woman in the elevator
is unbelievable, huh?
- [LAUGHS]
- Hey, sis!
[FYANG] It was really you, huh?
[GIGGLES]
What if she only wanted
to give you some advice?
You know what?
That was a very detailed story.
- They knew everything.
- It was the full story.
You'd need to be a great writer
to come up
with a story like that.
And I think something
like that can happen.
I mean...
[VICE] But like...
[TETAY] You're unsure?
It's possible that
the girl was a bit drunk.
- Right.
- They were in a party.
- And she thought--
- [VICE] Was she drunk?
But she's very...
That girl was very careless.
She must've been brave.
And that girl
saw me at the event.
- So like--
- Why didn't she invite you?
Right.
I mean, I'm okay with that.
Like, hello.
It's okay she didn't invite me.
She probably wanted
something to happen.
Did you feel uncomfortable?
I don't know how to translate
those kinds of things.
[VICE] But why did you
tell Fyang about it?
- You told Fyang, right?
- Yes.
How did she find out?
Did you tell her?
I went up to my floor,
and I was with JP that time.
[FYANG] Yeah.
[VICE] Uh...
- [CROWD SCREAMS]
- [VICE] Who's that?
We were fighting--
- JP?
- Who's that?
- He said JP.
- Um, I meant--
- Who is JP?
- Nobody.
[CROWD SCREAMING]
- Who's that?
- What?
He's one of our batchmates.
- He's our batchmate.
- In  PBB?
- Oh, JP.
Not in  PBB,   uh...
[JM] Just our batchmate.
He went up with me
to pick Fyang up.
- Yes.
- Oh.
We all met up kind of late.
But we all wanted to
spend time together.
- Yeah.
- So we went upstairs.
I say  Trot.
[AUDIENCE CLAMORING]
I mean, they even have an
extra character in the story.
I think it's a true story.
Right.
and the way Fyang
was telling the story,
and even JM,
it was very detailed.
Did it get on your nerves?
When that happened,
did you get annoyed,
or you didn't
think much about it?
- [VICE] Tell us the truth.
- No.
[VICE] No?
- She's confident.
- It didn't annoy me.
But why did you have to say
that she saw you at the event?
It's like...
- I'm prettier.
- [VICE] Okay.
- [CROWD EXCLAIMS]
- Ah!
If you had a chance to
talk to her that night,
what would you have told her?
Nothing.
I'm not confrontational.
Especially when we're
in an event like that
with many people.
And if I did end up seeing her,
I would be sarcastic.
[VICE] Like?
I'd ask why she invited JM,
but not me.
I'd ask if she had
an ulterior motive.
[CROWD LAUGHS]
[VICE] I say  Trot.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[AUDIENCE CLAMORING]
- Me too.
- Same here.
What about you?
-  Trot!
Do you know who it is?
- Yes!
- Did you tell them?
- No.
Why did they say yes?
Y'all are playing.
[TETAY] I say Trot!
- Me too.
- I could feel her fuming.
- You can feel she's pissed.
- Yes.
- I can feel it.
- So...
What is the deep truth
in that statement?
Is it  Trot   or  Charot?
It's...  Trot.
[AUDIENCE CLAMORING]
Yeah.
Who is she?
But I applaud you
for being very secure.
Yeah, because I knew
he wasn't going to go up.
Because I would've
confronted that person.
- Same here.
- I didn't see her after that.
I even wrote a song
about girls like that.
I wrote a song about that.
I really did.
I would've confronted her.
- You were the bigger person.
- [FYANG] Yes.
And it wasn't about
not confronting her.
But I told myself
I wouldn't go that low.
I didn't stoop to her level.
Oh, very good!
- That's correct.
- And...
...this is some real talk.
He's afraid of you when it
comes to things like that.
Like one time,
I think we were in Canada...
- Remember?
- Why?
I'm serious.
They were watching
something in my room.
Vhong was there
with other people.
Jarren and I were there too.
Jarren needed to get
something from their room,
and they were
roommates that time.
- [FYANG] Oh, okay.
- I woke him up.
I told him we were
getting some drinks.
I invited him to drink
with us in my room.
He nodded like this.
He told me you wouldn't
want him to do that.
I don't want her
to get surprised.
Fyang might get surprised
I'm not here.
Then she'd ask me why
I'm inviting you to my room.
[FYANG LAUGHS]
I mean, she'll be surprised if
I went out without her knowing.
- I'm fine with that.
- They hung out there.
I invited JM.
But he already had
a sleep mask on.
- An eye mask?
- Yeah.
- Sleeping mask?
- His eyes were covered.
I told him he might
feel left behind,
because everyone
was in my room.
But he said he
was okay with it.
You've got a hold on him.
Told you, girl!
Right?
Well, nice try.
[LAUGHING]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING, CLAPPING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Nicely said.
And because
some of you were wrong,
you will be punished again.
Your punishment will be...
to fetch the paper bills
hidden in the flour
using your mouth.
You cannot use your hands.
Where is the flour?
Bring it over here.
[TETAY] Bring in the bills.
This is Fyang's fault. [GIGGLES]
[VICE] Looks like someone
wants to confront her.
Why'd you have to share that?
Kidding!
Why'd you have to
tell them about it?
But JM and Fyang
didn't mention any names, okay?
I don't want people
making assumptions.
Don't drag innocent people
into this issue.
[TETAY] They mentioned
her gender, not her name.
Yes. So, let's leave it at that.
Here we go again.
[VICE] So, they're looking
for paper bills.
Okay. How many
are they looking for?
Just one bill.
One, two, three, go!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICE] Verna, are you just
fixing your makeup?
You're not getting anything.
Where's the bill?
This is the Deep Truth,
so we placed the bill
eep in that bowl.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VICE] While they search
for the paper bills,
the three of us
will have some fun over here.
What do you have
in store for everyone?
Let's go.
Yes, guys,
coming very soon,
Haunted Carnival.
In cinemas on December 25
for the MMFF.
And watch out for
Will You Fake Marry Me?
Season 2
streaming soon on iWant.
[VICE] Yes, and your film
is in Netflix's Top 10.
Yes, guys.
Thank you so much, everyone.
If you haven't watched
Almost Us,
it is now available on Netflix.
And watch out for
JM's  One for the Road.
It's still in production,
but stay tuned.
[VICE] Are you JM's handler?
[LAUGHS]
You're his promo manager?
And Big Brother's house is
reopening this October, right?
Yes, stay tuned this October.
[VICE] They found the bill!
Show it to us!
Perfect!
Thank you, JM and Fyang.
Thank you very much.
- Did you have fun?
- We did!
Thank you for having us.
They had fun.
Did you have fun?
- Yes!
You may have missed
some parts,
but thank you so much
for watching us on GMA.
If you want to watch
the moments that were cut,
just visit iWant
because you can stream the
GGV Unfiltered Version   there.
Feel the laughter worldwide.
Subscribe to iWant.
Thank you to Moodism
Furniture Design House
for the beautiful set pieces
we have here at the studio.
Kapamilya, Kapuso,
see you next week
here at your favorite
Sunday night habit...
[IN UNISON]
Gandang Gabi Vice!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]